{"data": {"https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Rz4rOsO2-nO9yfjzovQXYtXWJxSyvoo5/view?usp=sharing": {"topic": "0", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Rz4rOsO2-nO9yfjzovQXYtXWJxSyvoo5/view?usp=sharing", "answer": "45151"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HRZbk8niVVbGXxBwZHfwoU2TwuGNcN12/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "0", "difficulty": "1", "origin": "quiz1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HRZbk8niVVbGXxBwZHfwoU2TwuGNcN12/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "1870"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1sKi_rtQCMiM7rBsAPcLEfDsV1POnq67X/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "1", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1sKi_rtQCMiM7rBsAPcLEfDsV1POnq67X/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "dbabd dbadba\ndcc"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1aE9d4tFZ9JCo2htb-G9rKGIkFndIvl_f/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "3", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1aE9d4tFZ9JCo2htb-G9rKGIkFndIvl_f/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "([5, 1], [5, 2, 4, 5])\n[2]"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1CDsXM_9QVR7y_9Yoywl2tsUPuZ9itOjF/view?usp=sharing": {"topic": "3", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "quiz2,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1CDsXM_9QVR7y_9Yoywl2tsUPuZ9itOjF/view?usp=sharing", "answer": "[4, 1] [4, 5, 2] [4, 1, 3]"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HGCFwwlNvr0wwlOauMg2ByW3XkzsSOxx/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "3", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "quiz3,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HGCFwwlNvr0wwlOauMg2ByW3XkzsSOxx/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "[2, 3] [2, 3] [1, 2, 3, 3]\nTrue False"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ossue6AokF_7V9ziH9lP7er_gPmy6l7W/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "3", "difficulty": "1", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ossue6AokF_7V9ziH9lP7er_gPmy6l7W/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "[-1, -1]"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GfPON0LQzQh72afleBvF8eTrCEZ3w4qs/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "4", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GfPON0LQzQh72afleBvF8eTrCEZ3w4qs/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "([[4, 6], [5]], [[2, 3], [4], 5])\n[[4, 6]]"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/15BBA5AJlGJObYMeM5IG1_TwALiVeS8QL/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "4", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "midterm1,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/15BBA5AJlGJObYMeM5IG1_TwALiVeS8QL/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "[1, 2]\n[[3], [2, 3], [2, 3], [4]]"}, "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1lk-_SOCVWyUwG_ADLOBZCwrSf-jb-tUv/view?usp=share_link": {"topic": "4", "difficulty": "0", "origin": "quiz4,3", "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1lk-_SOCVWyUwG_ADLOBZCwrSf-jb-tUv/view?usp=share_link", "answer": "([[5], [8], [8]], [[8], [6, 7], [8]])\n[[6, 3], [6, 3], [8]]"}}}